Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2011-071
  - Latin America in the News 4/4, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - LAS News at Stanford 1/2, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - LAS News at Stanford 2/2, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Curricula on the Web 1/5, 35886 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Curricula on the Web 2/5, 35886 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Curricula on the Web 3/5, 35886 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Curricula on the Web 4/5, 35886 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Curricula on the Web 5/5, 35886 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Enrollments- Latin American Studies 1/2, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments- Latin American Studies 2/2, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Evaluations 1/3, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Evaluations 2/3, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations 3/3, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 1/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 2/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 3/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 4/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 5/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 6/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 7/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 8/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 9/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University - Syllabi 10/10, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CLAS Events 1/3, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CLAS Events 2/3, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CLAS Events 3/3, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CLAS Events, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - CLAS Events 1/2, 1994 Fall - 1995 Spring (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CLAS Events 2/2, 1994 Fall - 1995 Spring (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CLAS Events 1/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CLAS Events 2/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CLAS Events 3/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - CLAS Events 4/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CLAS Events 5/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - CLAS Events 6/6, 1993 Fall - 1994 Spring (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CLAS Events 1/4, 1992 Fall - 1993 Spring (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CLAS Events 2/4, 1992 Fall - 1993 Spring (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CLAS Events 3/4, 1992 Fall - 1993 Spring (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CLAS Events 4/4, 1992 Fall - 1993 Spring (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CLAS Events 1/4, 1990 Fall - 1992 Spring (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - CLAS Events 2/4, 1990 Fall - 1992 Spring (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - CLAS Events 3/4, 1990 Fall - 1992 Spring (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - CLAS Events 4/4, 1990 Fall - 1992 Spring (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - LAS Syllabi 1/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - LAS Syllabi 2/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - LAS Syllabi 3/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - LAS Syllabi 4/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - LAS Syllabi 5/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - LAS Syllabi 6/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - LAS Syllabi 7/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - LAS Syllabi 8/8, 1998 Spring - 2004 Fall (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - LAS Syllabus 1/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - LAS Syllabus 2/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - LAS Syllabus 3/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - LAS Syllabus 4/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - LAS Syllabus 5/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - LAS Syllabus 6/6, 1982-1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 2000-20001 (Box 13, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, undated (Box 13, Folder Album)
  - Bolivar House Party for Professor John Johnson, 26457 (Box 14, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1987-1992 (Box 14, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - Press Book Center for Latin American Studies - Stanford University, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder Album)
  - K-12 Community College Fellowship, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - K-12 Community College Fellowship, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Community College Fellowship, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship Information, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Website - Original Content, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Website - Updates, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Website - Technical, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Photos, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Photo Archives, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Funding Sheets - Master Document, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Daily, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Registrar, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Time Schedules, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Central American Working Group, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin - General, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for Reinstatement, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Samples - Other Institutions, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Publication Materials, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Historical Files, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Historical Files, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - GFS Information, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Articles and Photos - Raw Material, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Sample Publications, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - From Amy, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Original Site Content, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Site Reconstruction - Layout, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Site Reconstruction - Content, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CA Web Page Transparencies, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Website, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Asians in Latin America, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - New Brochures, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - enlace, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Visiting Scholars - Future, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Calendars - Fall, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Calendars - Winter, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Calendars - Spring, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Children in Detention Project, 33786 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chiapas Working Group, 34247 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Brazil Working Group, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures - Fall Notes (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures - Winter Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures - Spring Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Co-Sponsored Events - Fall, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Co-Sponsored Events - Winter, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Co-Sponsored Events - Spring, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Weekly Lecture Flyers - Copies, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Weekly Lecture Flyers - Copies - Fall, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Weekly Lecture Flyers - Copies - Winter, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Weekly Lecture Flyers - Copies - Spring, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Other Outreach - SPICE, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Funding Opportunities, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Calendars - Fall, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Calendars -Winter, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Calendars - Spring, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Co-Sponsored Events - Spring, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures - Winter Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Brown Bag Lunch Lectures - Spring Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Working Groups - Andean Archaeology, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Working Groups - Brazil, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Working Groups - Education, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Working Groups - Environment, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Working Groups - Latin American Law, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Working Groups - Mexican Studies, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Weekly Lecture Flyers All Years - Master (Originals), undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Cancelled and Pending Events - Ricardo Maduro Visit, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Cancelled and Pending Events - Enrique Oltuski Lecture, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Cancelled and Pending Events - Jonathan Moller Exhibit, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - CLAS Flyers - Originals, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Event Solicitations (Declined), undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - enlace Ideas, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Course Flyers Copies - Fall, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Course Flyers Copies - Winter, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Course Flyers Copies - Spring, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sign-Up Sheets - Attendance Forms, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - LCTL Conference, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Conferences and Event Logistics, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Conferences and Event Logistics - Lodging, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Conferences and Event Logistics - Room and Scheduling on Campus, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Conferences and Event Logistics - Meeting Services, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Conferences and Event Logistics - Travel (Visa Information), undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Events and Speakers, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Advertising, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Advertising, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin - Guideline Documents, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin - Old Courses, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin - New Courses, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Working Groups - Agendas, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Working Groups - Brazil, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Working Groups - Central America and the Caribbean, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Working Groups - Cine Latinoamericano, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Working Groups - Cuba, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Working Groups - Education, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Working Groups - Indigenous Peoples, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Working Groups - Mexican Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Rosencranz, Armin, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ramirez, Francisco (Education) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Rosset, Peter, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Saldivar, Ramon, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sierra, Ana M, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Jeffrey (FRI) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Business School - Wells, Robin E, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Yanagisako, Sylvia (Anthro) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Weiler, Hans (Education), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Szeienyi, Szonja (Sociology) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Urruela, Maria Cristina, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Naylor, Roz - Fellow, IIS, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Predmore, Michael (Span & Port), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Perales, Otilia Consuelo, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Pirie, Sophie, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Porras, Jerry (GSB) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Patell, James (GSB) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Matson, Pamela, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Manuelli, Rodolfo (GSB) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Marks, Patrice G (Spanish & Portugese), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mahood, Gail - Earth Science, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Mabry, Linda, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Lopez, Gerald (Law) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Krasner, Stephen D (Poli Sci), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Kennedy, Don, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Kenna, Caridad, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hing, Bill Ong (Law) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Klein, Herb, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Hunt, Patrick, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Hahn, Juergen (Span & Port) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Haro, Maria Paz (Span & Port), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Gumbrecht, Hans, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Gregg, Robert (Religious Studies), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Abernethy, David (Political Science) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Anderson, Susan, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Angelelli, Claudia Viviana, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Basch, Paul (Medicine), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Chafee, Steven (Communication), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Collier, George (Anthropology), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Collier, Jane (Anthropology), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Corral, Wilfrido (Span & Port), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Crow, Ben (FRI), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford M (Sociology), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Drake, Sandra (English) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Ebron, Paulla (Anthropology) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Einaudi, Marco (Earth Science), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Felsteiner, John (English) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Falcon, Walter (FRI) (supporting), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Fuenzalida, Edmundo (Overseas Prog) (Staff - Director Chile Program), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Gould, William B (Law), 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Film & Literature - Ruffinelli, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Ruffinelli Proposal - Film & Literature, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - LAS Tinker/Nabucco Nominees, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Valladares, Jose Augusto (Nabuco Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Benzaquen, Ricardo, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Berquo, Elza (Nabuco), 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Buarque, Cristovam (Nabuco Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Buarque de Hollanda, Heloisa (Nabuco Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Cardoso, Ruth & Fernando Henrique, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Campos, Roberto (Nabuco Nominee), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Jose Murilo, De Carvalho, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Flecha de Lima, Paulo Tarso (Nabuco Nominee), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Freire, Paulo (Nabuco Nominee), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Lamounier, Bolivar (Nabuco Nominee), 1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lutzenberger, Jose (Nabuco Nominee), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Sader, Emir (Nabuco Nominee), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Pojo do Rego, Antonio Carlos, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Salati, Eneas (Nabuco Nominee), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Schwartz, Roberto (Nabuco Nominee), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ehrenberg, Felipe (Tinker), 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Tinker & Nabuco Nomination Forms, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Portillo, Kourdes - Visiting Professor (Spanish & Portugese), 2001 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Mont-Reynaud, Henry - Haiti Course, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Alves, Jose Augusto Lindgren, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mota, Carlos Guillermo, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Goldemberg, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Amayo, Enrique, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Schwarcz, Lilia Katri Moritz (Nabuco Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Dresser, Denise (Tinker), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Dominguez, Nora (Tinker), undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Diaz Vallinam, Elvira (Tinker), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - De Riz, Liliana (Tinker), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - De Aguiar Tostes, Sergio Francisco (Tinker), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Costa Lima, Luiz (Tinker Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Creamer, German (Tinker), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Schwarz, Roberto (Nabuco Nominee), 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Alegre, Marcelo, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Rischmoller, Leonardo, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Wolf de Aguiar, Flavio, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Da Silva, Janice Theodoro, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Tinker Nominations, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Torres, Carlos Alberto (Tinker), undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Valenzuela, Luisa (Tinker), undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Varas, Augusto (Tinker), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Vilas, Carlos (Tinker), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Tinker Nominations, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cheresky, Isidoro (Tinker), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cardenas, Enrique (Tinker), 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Campos de Oliveira Faria, Jose E. (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Campero, Guillermo (Tinker), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Canclini, Nestor Garcia (Tinker), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Arizpe, Lourdes (Tinker), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Arrate, Jorge (Tinker), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Bueno Magano, Octavio (Tinker), 1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Brunner, Jose Joaquin (Tinker), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Blanch, Juan M Lope (Tinker), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Bouzas, Roberto (Tinker), 1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Basim Chuaqui, Rolando (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Aspe, Pedro (Tinker), 1996 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Arrate, Jorge Felix, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Alva, Walter (Tinker Nominee), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Paranagua, Paulo Antonio (Tinker Nominee), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Tinker Ideas, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Diamela, Eltit (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Fabregas Puig, Andres (Nominee), 1991 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Fajnzylber, Fernando (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Feldman-Bianco, Bela (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Feijoo Docampo, Maria del Carmen (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Fernandez, Jesus (CV), undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Ferrero Costa, Eduardo (Tinker), 1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Flisfich, Angel (Tinker), 1989 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Garreton Merino, Manuel Antonio (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Grases, Pedro (Tinker), undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Hernandez-Delgado, Alejandro, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Hernandez, Rafael (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Hirst, Monica (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Huneeus, Carlos (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Jaramillo, Felipe (Tinker), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Jimenez Godinach, Guadalupe (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Kaliman, Ricardo (Tinker), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Larrain Bascunan, Felipe (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Lisboa Bacha, Edmar (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Lomnitz Adler, Claudio (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Ludmer, Josefina (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Martinez-Alier, Juan (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Mata, Leonardo (Tinker), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Medina, Ernesto (Tinker), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Meyer Cosio, Lorenzo (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Millones, Luis (Tinker), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Monreal, Pedro (Tinker), 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Monterroso, Augusto (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Neves, Walter (Tinker), 1990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Moreno Ocampo, Luis (Tinker), 1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Moreira Alves, Maria Helena (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Pereira Paiva, Vanilda (Tinker), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Paranagua, Paulo Antonio (Tinker Nominee) (CV), undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Perez de Cuellar, Javier (Tinker), 1993 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Guido Pincione (Tinker), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Portocarrero, Gonzalo (Tinker), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Prieto Gonzalez, Alfredo (Tinker), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Ramirez-Grossman, M Pilar (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Rivano, Juan O (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Roa Bastos, Augusto (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Simao Sader, Emir (Tinker), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Sirvent, Maria Teresa (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Stavenhagen, Rodolfo (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Stolcke, Verena (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Szekely, Gabriel (Tinker), undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Guzman, Patricio (Tinker), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2012-059
  - Interview with Fernando Cardoso, 1981 Dec; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Sponsored by the Joint Center for Latin American Studies, UCB and Stanford.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH.2015-050
  - Capstone Journal. Master of Arts in Latin American Studies, Stanford University., 2014 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-272
  Capstone Projects.
  - Chappel H. Lawson, Building the Fourth Estate, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Hector Perla, Neoliberal Reforms in El Salvador, 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)
  - Andres Small, The Cuban Promise for Tomorrow Case Studies on the Perspectives and Aspirations of Cuba's Youth, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)
  - Sexual Harrassment in Chile: Origins, Existence, Perspectives, 1996 Mar (Box 1)
  - Course reading for L.A.S. 126 The Politics of Environmental Degradation in Latin America, 1994 Spring (Box 1)
  - Course readings for Latin American Studies 251, 1992 Winter (Box 1)
  - The Changing of the Guard: The United States in Haiti, 1915-1993, 1993 Sep (Box 1)
  - The Political Economy of Privatization in Brazil, 1996 Jun (Box 1)
  - The Militarization of Honduras in the 1980's, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Debating Feminisms: The Latin American and Caribbean Feminist Encuentros (1981-1996), 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Museos Para la Paz. Propuesta Para la Definicion de un Nuevo Concepto de Museo Historico en Guatemala, 2000 Jul (Box 1)
  - Bridging the Linguistic Divide: A Study on How a Self-Help Center Assists Spanish-Speaking Latinos Achieve Meaningful Access to the California Courts, 2009 Jun (Box 1)
  - Texaco in Ecuador's Oriente Region: Towards a Theory of Transborder Legal Disputes, 1998 Jun 9 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Detras de los Nosotros que Ustedes Ven, Detras Estamos Ustedes: Renegotiating Citizenship in Zapatista Communities, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 20 Years After the Revolution: Nicaragua's Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional in the Opposition, 2000 Jun (Box 1)
  - Ecuador: Caught in the Stalemate of Crises, 2001 Jun (Box 1)
  - Master of Arts in Latin American Studies Stanford University Capstone Journal Class of 2012, 2012 Jun (Box 1)
  - Chappel H. Lawson, Building the Fourth Estate, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Hector Perla, Neoliberal Reforms in El Salvador, 1998 Jun (Box 1)
  - Carlos Gervasoni, Economic Policy and Electoral Performance in Latin America, 1982-1995, 1995 Sep 12 (Box 1)